codexworld.com 2018-01-26

# Privacy Policy - CodexWorld

**[codexworld.com](http://www.codexworld.com/) respect visitors privacy and it is much important to us. The following statements describe the privacy policy of [codexworld.com](http://www.codexworld.com/). This privacy policy applied to the site and all products, contents & services offered by CodexWorld.**

**Personal Identification Information:**  
[codexworld.com](http://www.codexworld.com/) requires no user registration. Users are free to visit at [codexworld.com](http://www.codexworld.com/), navigate all its pages, read all tutorials, view demos and download scripts. We are collecting personal information when visitors fill out a form, subscribe our newsletter and try the tutorial demo at our site.

**Logs:**  
Whenever you access our website [codexworld.com](http://www.codexworld.com/) maintains log files. The following information are stored into the log file.

  * Your IP address,
  * Internet Service Provider,
  * Type of browser,
  * Operating system,
  * date and time,
  * Reffrer website and
  * Entry & exit pages.

**Link to Other Websites:**  
[codexworld.com](http://www.codexworld.com/) contains many links to other websites that not owned or controlled by Us. We are not responsible for the privacy of such third party websites and our privacy does not govern you to use such other websites. Our policy only applies to information collected by [codexworld.com](http://www.codexworld.com/). We request you to be aware before leaving our site and to read the privacy policy of such third party websites.

**Cookies:**  
Our site uses “cookies” to enhance visitors experience and improve the speed of our site. We do not use cookies to collect any personal information or sensitive information.

Cookies on [codexworld.com](http://www.codexworld.com/) are used by ourselves and our third party vendors. Cookies are used for the following reason.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to this website.
  * Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to this website.
  * You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).)

Also, we use cookies to collect visitor statistics and this helps us to improve our website. 

Google Analytics – We use Google Analytics for tracks visitors and website traffic statistics. It may collect visitor’s location, IP or any other information. Privacy Policy of Google Analytics is owned by Google.

**Your Acceptance of Privacy Policy:**  
By using this site, you agree of this policy. If you do not agree on this policy, please do not access our site.

 If you want any other information or have any queries about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at contact@codexworld.com.
